Lê Tử Tuấn

Date of birth 22/01/2000

Gender Male

Phone 0396694769

Email tutuanletkpt@gmail.com

Address 78/K4, Công Hoa, Tan Binh, Ho Chi Minh

Website github.com/TuTuanLe

OBJECTIVE

With over three years in web development, including three years with React.js and two years with Node.js, I have developed strong skills in building and maintaining robust applications. I am confident in my ability to contribute effectively to your Node.js team and am eager to further develop my skills as a professional software engineer. I look forward to bringing my expertise and enthusiasm to your company.

-----O-----

Portfolio: https://profile-tanh0309.vercel.app/

EDUCATION

Aug 2018 - May 2024

University of Information Technology VNU-HCM

Information System

WORK EXPERIENCE

Feb 2023 - May 2024

ZMP Vietnam

Middle / Software Engineer

- Build back-end components by leveraging ACID compliance, normalization and sub-queries to streamline intricate and expensive queries across multiple tables.
 Elevated trigger mechanisms for production, resulting in a remarkable efficiency boost.
- Carrying out unit testing using Jest and end-to-end tests using Cypress.
- Perform code reviews with other team members' code.
- Optimize applications for maximum speed and scalability.
- Write and review technical documents covering the design and implementation of features.

June 2022 - Feb 2023

ZMP Vietnam

Junior / Software Engineer

- Developed a cutting-edge booking solution REST APIs using Express,
 PostgresDB, and MongoDB, seamlessly integrated with a IOT service.
- · Implementing High order component
- Developing the RESTful APIs, as per the client requirement.
- Performed unit testing for RESTful API using Jest framework.
- Handling Front End design using Antd
- Improve performance on monitoring page, achieved a reduction in rendering time by 20% and increased overall user engagement by 15%
- · Dynamic json form support for UI
- · Notification to slack channel

Nov 2021 - Dec 2022	 META-UP Korea (Freelancer) Fresher / Frontend Developer I was working a freelance frontend developer at Meta-Up remotely. Created a responsive frontend website in desktop and mobile version from a given design at Figma using React Js. Integrating REST APIs from the backend team and implementing logic. Developed behavioral react apps with interactive UIs using one-way data flow and virtual DOM concepts. Created reusable components to enhance efficiency and foster code reusability. Effectively utilized props, context, and Redux for efficient state management.
May 2021 - July 2021	 DTN SOLUTION Intern / Frontend Developer Fixing bugs and developing new features on the platform using, HTML, CSS, React JS Refactoring code to create scalable, reusable code. Create new page list animal Responsible for React UI components

SKILLS

Front End	HTML / CSS / JavaScript / ES6 / TypeScript / ReactJS / SwiftUI
Library	Ant-Design / Tailwind / Styled-Components / SCSS
Back End	Node.js / Express.js / MongoDB / MySQL / Redis / Socket.IO / PostgreSQL / dynamoDB / Sql Server
Cloud services	AWS (Cloud Watch / S3 / EC2 / Step Functions / Lambda / serverless)
os	Linux / MacOS

LANGUAGES

English Language Skills:

- TOEIC Score: 500
- Proficient in listening and reading comprehension in English.
- Capable of understanding a wide range of topics and written materials.

PROJECTS

ROBOHI-FLATFORM-FRONTEND

(Jun 2022 - May 2024)

Customer	Japan
Description	 FROBO-HI, a cloud-based multi-robot OS, is a system that comprehensively manages robots on a facility or city basis. By linking with equipment such as robots and elevators, and various business systems, it is possible to operate robots without human intervention. We also provide analysis functions to make robot utilization more efficient.
Team size	40
My position	Software Engineer

My responsibilities	 Dispatch task request for robot delivery. Fleet/Operations Management: Registration and management of robot, user, and facility informationMap integration function (point cloud, CAD, BIM, images) Setting routes, pauses, and passing areas Task scheduling management, and on-demand instructions. Control/monitoring Driving management: Using group control algorithms Real-time operation monitoring Alert/notification function Remote control
Technologies used	ReactJS, ExpressJS, NestJS, RxJS, AWS Service

ROBOHI-FLATFORM-BACKEND

(Oct 2022 - May 2024)

Customer	Japan
Description	A backend platform designed to integrate robots and devices is a foundation that provides services and communication to manage, control, and interact with automated devices.
Team size	20
My position	Software Engineer
My responsibilities	 Interlocking function between elevator and robotCooperation with security doors, fire alarm systems, And third-party integration: fire alarm, elevator, auto door, security gate, Developing the RESTful APIs for facility, robot and equipment. Notification to slack channel
Technologies used	ReactJS, ExpressJS, NestJS, RxJS, AWS Service

RFIS-FRONTEND

(Mar 2023 - May 2024)

Customer	Japan
Description	 RFIS, a cloud-based multi-robot OS, is a system that comprehensively manages robots on a facility in hospital By linking with equipment such as robots and elevators, and various business systems, it is possible to operate robots without human intervention. We also provide analysis functions to make robot utilization more efficient.
Team size	6
My position	Software Engineer
My responsibilities	 Alert/notification function for system Real-time operation monitoring By linking with equipment such as robots and elevators, and various business systems, it is possible to operate robots without human intervention. Map integration function (point cloud, CAD, BIM, images)
Technologies used	ReactJS, ExpressJS, NestJS, RxJS, AWS Service

RFIS-BACKEND

(Mar 2023 - May 2024)

Customer	Japan
Description	A backend platform designed to integrate robots and devices is a foundation that provides services and communication to manage, control, and interact with automated devices support for hospital
Team size	5
My position	Software Engineer
My responsibilities	 Third-party integration: fire alarm, elevator, auto door, security gate, Developing the RESTful APIs for facility, robot Notification to slack channel
Technologies used	ReactJS, ExpressJS, NestJS, RxJS, AWS Service

CHIBAZOO-TABLET

(Jun 2023 - Oct 2023)

Customer	Japan
Description	Table app support for robot carrying people around the park in chiba demo: https://www.zmp.co.jp/news/pressrelease_20240222
Team size	1
My position	Frontend Engineer
My responsibilities	 Display UI for parking, departure, user can choose any course the robot will run to the point they choose, The screen will display a google map with the robot's current location, arrow for direction, Battery percentage robots and markers for animals. Handle robots start trip with solo or pairing
Technologies used	React Native, Socketio, RxJS, Map, AWS MQTT,

EYECAN-PARKING-IOT

(Apr 2023 - Oct 2023)

Customer	Japan
Description	Parking assistance application Live: https://www.zmp.co.jp/eyecan
Team size	6
My position	IOS Developer
My responsibilities	 Using camera frustum to detect left and right or visible mode Scanning the QRCode, auto-dim, Show arrow for direction in drivable, Computed distance
Technologies used	SWIFT, ARKit, NODEJS

TENQUBE-VISUALOMS (META-UP)

(Jan 2022 - Mar 2022)

Customer	Korea
Description	An order management system for logistics center managers and an app for store owners are provided, allowing them to manage products and check orders. live: https://www.tenqube.com/products/visual-order
Team size	6
My position	Frontend Developer
My responsibilities	Order management system page, analytic order page, homepage, contact page, portfolio card,
Technologies used	ReactS, Redux, TypeScript

TENQUBE-HUB (META-UP)

(Mar 2022 - Dec 2022)

Customer	Korea
Description	An order management system for logistics center managers V1
Team size	6
My position	Frontend Developer
My responsibilities	calculate page, inquiry page, order page, statictic page, review page,
Technologies used	ReactJS, Redux, TypeScript

METAUP-LANGING(META-UP)

(Dec 2021 - Jun 2022)

Customer	Korea
Description	Langing page live: https://meta-up.com/

Team size	1
My position	IOS Developer
My responsibilities	Implement UI Home, Features, Testimonials, Contact page
Technologies used	ReactJS

WEDDING-CHECK (META-UP)

(July 2021 - Nov 2021)

Customer	Korea
Description	WeddingCheck is your ultimate wedding planning companion, designed to streamline every step of the wedding preparation process. From creating guest lists to managing budgets and coordinating vendors, this app simplifies the complexities of planning your special day.
Team size	5
My position	Frontend Developer
My responsibilities	Vendor Reviews and Recommendations: Browse through a curated list of wedding vendors, read reviews from real couples, and request quotes directly through the app. implement financial tools, account info screen, notification screen, check phone screen,
Technologies used	React Native, Redux, TypeScript, Firebase

KADOKAWA (DTN-SOLUTION)

(May 2021 - July 2021)

Customer	Japan
Description	An immersive gaming experience that transports players into diverse landscapes filled with captivating wildlife.
Team size	5
My position	Frontend Developer
My responsibilities	Featured News, guide for new, list video, terms of service, parent page,
Technologies used	React JS, Three.js, Redux, TypeScript, Socket 10